Dear younger me,
I want you
to hear this.
Didi's inability to
love you well
was never a
proof that you
are unworthy of
love. No, you
were a child.
You were not
supposed to carry
the responsibility of
an adult inability
to love you
well. And younger
me, I want
you to listen
to this and
think about this
very carefully. Maybe
Daddy was available
physically, but emotionally
not available. And
maybe he was
available physically and
financially, but he
never told you
that I'm proud
of you. Younger
me. And that
made you ask
yourself, what is
wrong with me?
And maybe His
criticism made you
always ask yourself,
is ever anything
that I do
ever good enough?
And now you
have grown up.
You've become an
adult that constantly
need reassurance. You
always think that
people leave and
then you leave
first. You always
mistakenly mistaken boundaries
as a rejection.
Younger me, I
want you to
heal and heal
for yourself. And
your healing makes
you to raise
healthy kids because
if you don't
heal, it makes
you raise broken
children like the
way you were
raised. The book
of Psalms 10,
verse 10, the
book of Psalms
chapter 37, verse
10, it says,
though my father
and my mother
may reject me,
But God will
receive me. I
want you to
underline the word
receive. Young me,
God does not
look at you
as a broken
and rejected child.
He loves you.
He receives you.
He welcomes you.
All you can
do for yourself
right now is
to heal and
move on so
that you raise
healthy children and
you become a
good version of
yourself for you.